http://www.symphonysuites.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyIntroductionIn this policy, "we", "us" and "our" refer to Symphony Workplaces and affiliates.We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy. Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications and limit the publication of your information.Your Personal and Account DataWe may process data about your use of our website and services.
This usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analyzing the use of our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services and providing our services to our prospects and clients.We may process and store your personal and account data which may include your name, email address name, address, telephone number, and employment details.. The account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining our databases, and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.We may process information contained in any inquiry you submit to us regarding goods and/or services. This information may be processed for the purposes of offering, marketing and selling relevant goods and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is consent.We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website. This transaction data may include your contact details, your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate interests, namely our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.We may process notification data and information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters. The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent.We may process information contained in or relating to any communication or correspondence data that you send to us. The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.We may process any of your personal and account data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out below, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.Please do not supply any other person's personal data to us, unless we prompt you to do so.Providing Your Data to OthersWe may disclose your personal or account data to any affiliate or supplier of ours as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the legal bases, set out in this policy.We may disclose your personal or account data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.Financial transactions relating to our website and services may be handled by our payment services providers. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this section we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.You acknowledge that personal data that you submit through our website or services may pass through multiple communication channels and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.Retaining Personal DataPersonal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposesNotwithstanding the other provisions of this section, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.AmendmentsWe may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.We may notify you of changes to this policy by email or through our website.Your RightsYou may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you; provision of such information will be subject to supply of appropriate evidence of your identity. For this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a notary or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address.We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes.In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for our purposes set forth herein.
We will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes by contacting the Data Protection Officer below.About CookiesAdditional information regarding the categories and types of cookies used are listed in the dedicated Cookie Policy section, which is available at this site: https://www.symphonyworkplaces.com/cookie-policyData Protection OfficerData Protection OfficerSymphony Workplaces89 Headquarters PlazaMorristown, NJ 07960USAAttention: info@workplacesmail.comTelephone: 877-539-5100
Just Better.
